What If You Could Feel Like They Do... We Can Help.
Antiviral is a science fiction, horror film directed by Brandon Cronenberg.
Syd March is an employee at a clinic that sells injections of live
viruses harvested from sick celebrities to obsessed fans.
When he becomes infected with the disease that kills super sensation Hannah
Geist, Syd becomes a target for collectors and rabid fans.
He must unravel the mystery surrounding her death
before he suffers the same fate.
Syd March, played by Caleb Landry Jones.
Hannah Geist, played by Sarah Gadon.
Dr. Abendroth, played by Malcolm McDowell.
Arvid, played by Joe Pingue.
Dev Harvey, played by Sheila McCarthy.
Edward Porris, played by Douglas Smith.
Antiviral is a 2012 science fiction horror film
written and directed by Brandon Cronenberg.
The film competed in the Un Certain Regard section
at the 2012 Cannes Film Festival.
Cronenberg re-edited the film after the festival to make it
tighter, trimming nearly six minutes out of the film.
The revised film was first shown at the 2012 Toronto International Film Festival, and was a co-winner,
alongside Jason Buxton's Blackbird, of the festival's Best Canadian First Feature Film award.
The film explores themes of future, satire, celebrity, injection, metamorphosis.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.